<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IELTS Speaking</string>
    <string name="ielts_speaking">IELTS Speaking</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="listening">LISTENING</string>
    <string name="reading">READING</string>
    <string name="speaking">SPEAKING</string>
    <string name="writing">WRITING</string>
    <string name="overall_band_score">Overall Band Score</string>
    <string name="part_1_topics">Part 1 - Topics</string>
    <string name="part_2_topics">Part 2 - Topics</string>
    <string name="learned">Learned</string>
    <string name="part_1">Part 1</string>
    <string name="part_2">Part 2</string>
    <string name="part_3">Part 3</string>
    <string name="sample_answer">Sample answer</string>
    <string name="about_application">This application is made for those who wants to improve their speaking skills.</string>
    <string name="about_application2">Sample answers and sample video answers are the best tools for users. Especially, Recording voice aspects is one of the great ways of testing yourself.</string>
    <string name="about_application3">Hope you enjoy using application.</string>
    <string name="about_application4">I really hope you rate us 5 stars.</string>
    <string name="version">Version:</string>
    <string name="version_number">1.0.0</string>
    <string name="released">Released:</string>
    <string name="released_time">10.10.2022</string>
    <string name="target">Target:</string>
    <string name="target_item">IELTS Speaking</string>
    <string name="goals">Goals:</string>
    <string name="goal1">1. Improve Speaking</string>
    <string name="goal2">2. Improve Pronunciation</string>
    <string name="goal3">3. Increase Vocabulary</string>
    <string name="sample_answer_band_9">Sample answer\n Band 9</string>
    <string name="sample_answer_band_8">Sample answer\n Band 8</string>
    <string name="sample_answer_band_7">Sample answer\n Band 7</string>
    <string name="sample_answer_band_6">Sample answer\n Band 6</string>

    //work questions and answers
    <string name="workQ1">What do you do?</string>
    <string name="workA1">For the past few months, I\’ve been working for The Guardian as a news editor. This is my first job ever, and I\’m working hard to contribute to the success of this prestigious newspaper.</string>
    <string name="workQ2">What are your responsibilities?</string>
    <string name="workA2">As a part-time editor, I am responsible for editing news related to current affairs as well as collecting information for the newspaper edition.</string>
    <string name="workQ3">Why did you choose to do that type of work (or, that job)?</string>
    <string name="workA3">I guess it\’s mainly because of job flexibility and my passion for journalism. To be more specific, this job is unlike the nine-to-five work schedule, enabling me to find a better balance between work and life. Besides, this job gives me opportunities to pursue my dream to become a journalist.</string>
    <string name="workQ4">Is there some other kind of work you would rather do?</string>
    <string name="workA4">At present, I don\’t think I\’m able to dedicate myself to any other job. It\’s the experiences and opportunities I can gain that matters to me.</string>
    <string name="workQ5">Describe the company or organization you work for.</string>
    <string name="workA5">The Guardian is a national British daily newspaper which offers free access both to current news and an archive of three million stories. In April 2011, MediaWeek reported that The Guardian was the fifth most popular newspaper site in the world. I believe that the Guardian is the inspirational workplace for all people who dream of becoming a journalist.</string>
    <string name="workQ6">Do you enjoy your work?</string>
    <string name="workA6">I do, most of the time. Contributing to the news production for a world-class newspaper gives me a sense of satisfaction and pride. </string>
    <string name="workQ7">What do you like (or dislike) about your job?</string>
    <string name="workA7">Well, the perk of being a news editor is that you\’ll surround yourself with exciting news daily. What I don\’t like about this job is that I have to do a thousand edits to get to the final one that meets the requirement of my boss. Sometimes I feel a bit overloaded with tons of tasks.</string>
    <string name="workQ8">Do you miss being a student?</string>
    <string name="workA8">I missed student life once I got involved in the workplace. I think when I was a student, I had someone to guide me, whereas at work you must guide yourself. The academic environment was a comfort zone, and I struggled to fit in the working environment.</string>

    //study questions and answers
    <string name="studyQ1">Do you work or study?</string>
    <string name="studyA1">I am currently studying. I am in the 11th semester and my major is economics.</string>
    <string name="studyQ2">Where do you study?</string>
    <string name="studyA2">I study in the (…university name…). It is one of the best private universities in our country. My major is Economics.</string>
    <string name="studyQ3">What is the name of your college (or university)?</string>
    <string name="studyA3">The name of my university is (…say the full name of your university…). It is more popularly known as (…name that people call it in short…).</string>
    <string name="studyQ4">What subject are you studying?</string>
    <string name="studyA4">My major is Economics. I completed my school majoring commerce and studying in Economics was a long dream for me.</string>
    <string name="studyQ5">Which part of the course do you enjoy most?</string>
    <string name="studyA5">I enjoy learning new things in every semester. The project works in each semester is the part I enjoy most. These projects enable me to work in a group and hands on the theories I learn throughout the semester.</string>
    <string name="studyQ6">Why did you choose to study that?</string>
    <string name="studyA6">Honestly, I did not particularly select this subject. I attended the university admission test in commerce faculty and based on my performance on the exam and interview with the faculty members, I was offered this subject from their end. I wanted to study in commerce faculty and now I feel very lucky that I was offered this major.</string>
    <string name="studyQ7">Is it a difficult subject to study?</string>
    <string name="studyA7">In a general sense, this subject requires extensive study, research, group works and other academic activities. Things are new and challenging in many cases but I think with passion and dedication it can be conquered. To me, it is a difficult yet very enjoyable subject.</string>
    <string name="studyQ8">What is your favourite subject?</string>
    <string name="studyA8">Economics without any doubt is my favourite subject. I am very fascinated to discover the connection of this subject in our everyday life and the global economic structure has made it more complex yet more intriguing. I love to explore different theories and researches done on this subjects and how economics is all around us.</string>
    <string name="studyQ9">What kind of school did you go to?</string>
    <string name="studyA9">In my early childhood, I studied in a local English medium school and then was shifted to a government school by my parents when I was in grade 7. I was in a cantonment college and I have finished my twelve class degree from there. Now I am studying at a large university which is one of the best public universities in my country.</string>
    <string name="studyQ10">What was your favourite subject at school?</string>
    <string name="studyA10">Organisational behaviour, microeconomics were my two most favourite subjects so far. These two subjects have built my base and love for the whole course and I still find it fascinating.</string>
    <string name="studyQ11">What is the best thing about your university/school?</string>
    <string name="studyA11">I love my university life. The classes, friends, teachers, university life, my freedom to do so many things and my participation in some charity works organised by the university are equally important to me. If I have to select one best thing about my university, I would choose my exposure to a diverse culture and academic life that has motivated and inspired me to do even better than I initially thought. I was exposed to a life and era that was unimaginable to me and that is the best part of my university life so far.</string>
    <string name="studyQ12">What part of university life do you like best?</string>
    <string name="studyA12">Well, I think my previous answer already covers this answer. However, I would say I enjoy most of my university life and my exposure to a whole new culture that I never imagined is the best part of my university life. My university life offers me a vision for my future and potential jobs sectors and I think this is the best part.</string>
    <string name="studyQ13">What is the educational system like in your country?</string>
    <string name="studyA13">I am glad that you asked this question. In our country, the primary education is mandatory for all and it is funded by the government unless someone wants to send his kids to a private English medium school. The secondary and tertiary education systems are also managed and run by the government and private organisations. The government controlled educational institutes are less costly and the curriculums are presented and monitored by the education board. On the other hand, the private educational institutes are bound to include some of the national curriculums and they mostly follow their own syllabus. In all universities and in many colleges, higher education is offered in English. The technical and vocational colleges and universities are also popular in our country and they mostly offer certification and degree in selected technical and practical skill related fields. The private universities are approved by the Government controlled bodies and they have to follow their rules very strictly. I am happy to see many changes brought to our educational system in the last few years and innovation and quality modern education is a vision our country has already started implementing.</string>
    <string name="studyQ14">What are your future study plans?</string>
    <string name="studyA14">It will take me 7 months more or so to finish my graduation and then I will try to get admitted to a foreign university which has a reputation for better education. There I will complete my Master\’s degree and would get involved in a job. Besides doing the job I have plans to get enrolled in a professional MBS course to further my education. If time allows, I also wish to do some research based courses related to my academic background and interest.</string>
    <string name="studyQ15">What kind of job would you prefer after graduation?</string>
    <string name="studyA15">I would prefer to work in a multinational company which will offer me a position related to my academic background and have a positive working environment to learn and explore new things. I would not worry too much about my designation and salary initially but the company must have sufficient scope for career enhancement.</string>
    <string name="studyQ16">What is your career plan after you graduate?</string>
    <string name="studyA16">For the first few years, I will work in a multinational company. Then maybe in 10 years, I will plan to start my own business. I would like to be an entrepreneur rather than working in a company for the rest of my life. I know being an entrepreneur is not that easy and it requires a lot of dedication and commitment. However, I would work to fulfil this plan after I finish my graduation.</string>
    <string name="studyQ17">Why are you taking the IELTS test?  </string>
    <string name="studyA17">I am mainly taking the test to achieve a band score I require to apply in most of the reputed universities in Australia or Canada. As I have my plans to complete my Master\’s degree in a reputed foreign university, the IELTS score is a pre-requisite to prove my ability to handle the language – English, and I need the score to even apply to those universities.</string>

    //hometown questions and answers
    <string name="hometownQ1">What\’s (the name of) your hometown and where is it?</string>
    <string name="hometownA1">Victoria is my hometown. It is a province located in the west of my country.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ2">Is that a big city or a small place?</string>
    <string name="hometownA2">It is a small province with slightly more than 1 million people.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ3">Please describe your hometown a little?</string>
    <string name="hometownA3">It has a breathtaking view of picturesque landscapes with rolling mountains and greenish lakes. However, due to the increasing economy, a number of businesses, especially in sugarcane, are invested in my hometown making it very promising.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ4">How long have you been living there?</string>
    <string name="hometownA4">I had lived there for around 15 years before my family left for Santa City. It\’s been more than ten years since I left my hometown.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ5">Do you like your hometown? If yes, what do you like (most) about your hometown?</string>
    <string name="hometownA5">Yes, I do like my hometown! I like the hospitality of people in my hometown. Also, everyone was willing to give others a hand when they needed help.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ6">Is there anything you dislike about it?</string>
    <string name="hometownA6">Personally, it\’s a bit boring for me because as a small town, there isn\’t a shopping mall or any other means of entertainment. The streets don\’t get very crowded as well. However, I believe that it is improving day by day and turning into a potential hotspot due to the increasing number of annual visitors.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ7">Do you often visit your hometown?</string>
    <string name="hometownA7">I do visit occasionally when there are some celebrations. I also go on a long drive after some hectic weekends.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ8">Do you think you will continue living there for a long time?</string>
    <string name="hometownA8">To be honest, I hope I could go there to visit my relatives and friends, but settling down is not part of my plan. I am now getting familiar with city life as there are more job opportunities here.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ9">Has your hometown changed much since you were a child?</string>
    <string name="hometownA9">Actually yes. It has changed enormously. Around 20 years ago you would barely find tall buildings in my area, but now you\’d easily be able to catch sight of skyscrapers and tower blocks there.</string>
    <string name="hometownQ10">Are there any changes you would like to make in your hometown?</string>
    <string name="hometownA10">I would like to ameliorate the infrastructure so that I can avoid being stuck in a traffic jam during peak hours.</string>

    //home answers and questions
    <string name="homeQ1">What kind of housing/accommodation do you live in?</string>
    <string name="homeA1">For the past 21 years, I have lived in a house with my family. And I think if I can move out and start making a living on my own, I would try my best to have an independent place where I can plan and design a house layout to suit myself since sharing a room or a flat with strangers sounds so troublesome to me.</string>
    <string name="homeQ2">What do you usually do in your house/flat/room?</string>
    <string name="homeA2">Well, definitely I\’ll spend some time there. I study, I chill out by reading, drawing and dancing all by myself. Sometimes I also invite one or two friends to spend time with. We\’ll watch some movies together and tell each other endless stories.</string>
    <string name="homeQ3">Who do you live with?</string>
    <string name="homeA3">I live with my family. There are 5 of us and we all have our own room, which is way more comfortable as the older we grow, the more privacy we need for ourselves. I think our house is big enough for us yet still a warm and cosy place that I call home.</string>
    <string name="homeQ4">How long have you lived there?</string>
    <string name="homeA4">Although during my childhood my family had to move a lot, I\’ve lived in the most recent house for almost ten years. Comparing to the old houses, I think this house has been the best so far.</string>
    <string name="homeQ5">Do you plan to live there for a long time?</string>
    <string name="homeA5">The answer would be yes. My parents have been living there for a long time and moving in and out is too time-consuming and exhausting. Cleaning and arranging everything all over again would be like torture to them. For me, on the other hand, as I\’m thinking of moving out to start my adult life, hopefully soon I\’ll be able to afford to live in a flat or an apartment.</string>
    <string name="homeQ6">What\’s the difference between where you are living now and where you have lived in the past?</string>
    <string name="homeA6">As I\’ve already mentioned my family moved several times when I was younger. And the most current house where we’ve been living for about ten years is the best house so far. All of us have separate rooms for our need for privacy yet a big dining room where we can spend the whole evenings together watching TV or having dinner.</string>
    <string name="homeQ7">Can you describe the place where you live?/ Please describe the room you live in</string>
    <string name="homeA7">Briefly, my humble house locates in a small and quiet street, so coming home to me is like all the craziness happened outside is left behind. Just beside my house stands a big old tree. I have my own room with walls painted violet, which is kind of a peaceful colour. The air outside is fresh. I usually open the window to enjoy the wind and sunshine, which will help cool my room without an air conditioner. Since I spend most of my time staying at home, my room means the whole world to me. It\’s like a friend who is always there to share ups and downs with me. So yeah, I would always miss my house, my room whenever I\’m away.</string>
    <string name="homeQ8">Which part of your home do you like the most?</string>
    <string name="homeA8">It\’s the dining room where my family spends our time together.  Not only lunch or dinner but all our family reunions take place in the dining room where we can enjoy a harmonious atmosphere. We always try to keep the family dinner as something we cannot go a day without, since for us it\’s the family bonding that lies behind.</string>

    //Art
    <string name="artQ1"> Do you like art?</string>
    <string name="artA1">I have a lifelong passion for art since I was a child. Beside the official art class in school, I also joined a drawing class in The Children\’ House and my teachers were very pleased with my drawings. I also participated in some drawing competitions back then. Until now I still draw in my free time, although not as often as I used to do.</string>
    <string name="artQ2">Do you think art classes are necessary? (Why?)/ How do you think art classes affect children\’s development?</string>
    <string name="artA2">Yes, definitely. Learning arts, especially at a young age, can help stimulate children\’s cognitive development and encourage them to think outside the box. Because they\’re still little, their ideas are very fresh and lovely, which is worth appreciating.</string>
    <string name="artQ3">Are you good at art?</string>
    <string name="artA3">Art is a really vast subject, I believe and if it is about drawing things here and there, I would say I am pretty fine at it. But, I am surely not one of those who can make some masterpieces. I think I am good at it, all thanks to the art classes that I attended during my teen years. They were a great help during my growing years and taught me lot of creativity. Now, I can easily draw simple day to day things like pen or a face.</string>
    <string name="artQ4">What kind of paintings do people like?</string>
    <string name="artA4">In my opinion, people love hanging landscape paintings at home. Bringing in the beauty of Mother Nature somehow ease people\’s mind after a long day at work. Another style of drawing that most people also like is portrait. It could be portraits of someone important to them or even their lovely pets.</string>
    <string name="artQ5">What benefits can you get from painting as a hobby?</string>
    <string name="artA5">I think the mediation efficiency worth mentioning first. Colours in some ways reflect our thoughts and emotions very well and somehow stimulate our body to defend against our negativity inside. For me, in particular, I think what\’s so interesting about painting is that you have no idea how harmonized colours can become until you actually try.</string>
    <string name="artQ6">How often do you visit art galleries?</string>
    <string name="artA6">To tell you the truth, I have never visited art galleries before. Unless I have a guide to acknowledge me, art galleries would be quite boring for me.</string>
    <string name="artQ7">What kinds of things do you like to draw?</string>
    <string name="artA7">My main inspiration is Japanese manga. The drawing topic is extremely varied, however only manga seems to show great potency for my level. I have a big collection at home and as I sometimes go through it again, I can see how much I\’ve improved.</string>
    <string name="artQ8">Is it easy to learn how to draw?</string>
    <string name="artA8">I think I must say it\’s even challenging for a lot of people. I absolutely failed when it comes to drawing still life paintings like fruit and flowers. I think for those who succeed in drawing or arts in general, they first must have God-gifted talent, then comes to the long-term commitment to arts that requires extreme practice and high patience.</string>

    //Birthday
    <string name="birthdayQ1">How do children celebrate birthdays in your country?</string>
    <string name="birthdayA1">Children in my country celebrate their birthdays by inviting friends and relatives to their homes. They love to cut the cake and play indoor games at birthday parties.</string>
    <string name="birthdayQ2">How did you celebrate your last birthday?</string>
    <string name="birthdayA2">For my last birthday, I went on a two days trip to Zamin mountains with my family members. We went sightseeing and enjoyed a lot during that trip. My parents even kept a surprise party planned for me there. </string>
    <string name="birthdayQ3">What kinds of birthday gifts do you like to receive?</string>
    <string name="birthdayA3">On my birthdays, I like to receive handmade gifts such as cards, photo albums, etc. Also, I really love to receive storybooks as gifts.</string>
    <string name="birthdayQ4">Is there a difference between the way you celebrate your birthday in the past and in the present?</string>
    <string name="birthdayA4">Yes, in the past I used to invite my friends at home for a birthday party and my mother would cook food for us. But for the last two or three years, I like to go to a restaurant or cafe for parties with my friends.</string>
    <string name="birthdayQ5">How do you usually celebrate your birthday?</string>
    <string name="birthdayA5">I normally throw a party and invite all of my friends. Birthdays are a big thing in my family and in my culture, so we go all out when we celebrate them.</string>
    <string name="birthdayQ6">Are there any birthdays that are special in your culture?</string>
    <string name="birthdayA6">Yes, there a a few birthdays that are unique. These are the ones that occur when you are 13, 16,18,21 and 30. They usually have some connection to the law in the country, for example when you are 16 you are legally considered an adult and when you are 18 you can legally purchase alcohol or drive a car. </string>
    <string name="birthdayQ7">Can you remember a birthday you had as a child?</string>
    <string name="birthdayA7">Yes, the most memorable birthday I have ever had was when my mum and dad rented out a huge bouncing castle in secret and invited all my friends and family without telling me. I came home from school to find everyone waiting for me in my back garden. It was such a surprise!</string>

    //Childhood
    <string name="childhoodQ1">Did you enjoy your childhood?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA1">Yes, very much. My childhood was filled with lots of laughter, a great family of 3 generations, friends that were indispensable. My childhood was fun as I was free of worries because I had my basic needs met, and in instances where I was met with a challenge, there were family members ready to help and to encourage me to overcome it. In all, I really enjoyed being a child and often recalled the memories with a happy smile.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ2">What is your first memory of your childhood?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA2">On days when my grandmother held the hands of my twin and me as we walked to school is by far my freshest and deepest memory of childhood. On days when it rained, she would help us jump the puddles; on days when it was sunny, she was sure to have an umbrella. Walking hand-in-hand with smiles on our faces, she would tell us interesting stories of children who studied well in school and became great individuals. I must say the experience left an indelible mark.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ3">Did you have a lot of friends when you were a child?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA3">At school, I had lots of friends, perhaps partly because I am a twin and most people love twins and because I was an outgoing child. Even my teachers were my friends, and one still is as I\’ve kept in touch with her throughout the years. At home, my friends were numerous. They won\’t come to visit on weekends and spend lots of time with me playing house.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ4">What did you enjoy doing as a child?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA4">playing house was my most loved pastime. Putting jigsaw puzzles together was another thing I enjoyed as it was challenging and could involve my friends and me. At times when I was with friends, I loved to read the books of my elder siblings. Sometimes I understood a little of what was written in the books; other times, I didn\’t, but I just loved them though I usually got reprimanded for dirtying them.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ5">Do you think it is better for children to grow up in the city or in the countryside?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA5">there are positives and negatives to growing up in the city and to growing up in the countryside. Personally, I think it\’s better for children to grow up in the countryside where there is little to no pollution of the environment. In the countryside, there is access to fresh and healthy farm produce and as well as various fruits, even wild ones which contain natural vitamins and minerals to aid in the growth. In the countryside, where there are close-knit families, they learn about the value of family relationships and how everyone is interdependent.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ6">What was the best thing about your childhood?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA6">The best thing about my childhood has to be the fact that I made little friends. It was early in life that I had learnt that it is great to have friends but one can enjoy by oneself as well and that it is better if you have friends who will stick all through your life. I have been more independent because no one could ever tell me that I could not do it.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ7">What do you miss most about being a child?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA7">The best part about being a child is that no one cares how you look, because they look at your habits, your eyes, what you speak. It gives so much more freedom, when there is no sophistication associated with you, nothing to pretend, no one to impress and living life on your terms, in the present with no care about future.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ8">Do you think that children these days have a better or worse childhood than your generation? Why?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA8">I think definitely, children have a better childhood than our generation. Parents are now more aware and work on their children, developing the skills of their children.You can now see children working on things like cricket, music, dance activities. However, when it comes to general development, I think our generation was better. We were more aware of our families, we had stories to share, we had met our grandparents more often, heard stories from them and enjoyed life more better.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ9">What do you think is most important for a happy childhood?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA9">The most important thing for a happy childhood is a happy home. It is very important for a child to grow as a happy individual to have a home where his/her parents love each other. Where, there is a balance in life.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ10">What about your childhood do you wish you could change?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA10">If ever I could change one thing about my childhood, it would be my relation with my brother. For some reasons, I think we as children, never talked to each other much and it was later in life that I came to know that we both were two lonely souls and could have stuck together and enjoyed life as we grew up.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ11">Where did you grow up? How did that affect your childhood?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA11">I have grown up in different places because of my father\’s transfer. Travelling to different places as I grew up, taught me that we all are the same, fundamentally. As humans, we have the same problems and the same goals. It is just that some fight for them till the end, while others tend to lose hope and it is that one determination, love that changes and shapes our lives.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ12">What were some of your favorite activities when you were a child?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA12">I love cycling when I was a child. Cycling gave me the sense that I was free, that there was nothing that could stop me and I could just live the life as I want to and it was this feeling that made me love cycling even more. I remember, cycling during holidays and then evenings, even in the morning. I just loved it.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ13">Who, besides your parents, had the biggest impact on your childhood?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA13">I think as a child, my relatives had a very great impact on me. It was their opinions that have shaped to an extent the things that I believe in and the things that I do. It was when I started questioning their opinion, that I realized how fragile their opinion was, changing every minutes. It was through them that I learnt that we should just keep doing what we love.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ14">What do you want to provide your children that you didn\’t have when you were growing up?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA14">Feeling of the fact that I am their friend. Yes, this is one thing that I want my children to know, that no matter what, I am their friend and whatever is happening in their lives, they can share it with me. I want to know my issues and share with me theirs. I wish to have conversations like we have with our friends.</string>
    <string name="childhoodQ15">Who were you really jealous of when you were a child? Why were you jealous?</string>
    <string name="childhoodA15">As a child, I was jealous of those pretty girls in my class. I mean I used to wonder how could come school on time, wearing clean clothes and then score high in exams as well. I used to be the one who was always clumsy, figuring out things from here and there.</string>

    //Clothes
    <string name="clothesQ1">What colour clothes do you like to wear?</string>
    <string name="clothesA1">Well, I like to wear attires of all the colours, but mostly I prefer bright colours because light colours don\’t suit my personality and I don\’t feel comfortable whenever I wear light colour clothes.</string>
    <string name="clothesQ2">Do people in your country like to wear bright colours?</string>
    <string name="clothesA2">It is very hard to define the preference of all people for what colour they like. But yes I think that people like to wear bright colours in my country especially on special occasions like weddings because I always see everyone in bright colours at functions and marriages.</string>
    <string name="clothesQ3">What are the differences between men\’s and women\’s preferences in colour?</string>
    <string name="clothesA3">According to my perspective, there is no gender preference as I see both boys and girls wearing almost all colours. However, one colour that is most preferred by girls is pink, and I think black is more common among boys.</string>
    <string name="clothesQ4">What kind of clothes do you like to wear?</string>
    <string name="clothesA4">Well, I like to wear Punjabi suits because it defines my culture and tradition. Moreover, I feel comfortable while wearing my own traditional clothes.</string>
    <string name="clothesQ5">What kind of clothes do you never wear?</string>
    <string name="clothesA5">Honestly speaking, I never wear short clothes because they are not allowed in my culture and my family. Moreover, it looks awkward if someone wears shorts in my region.</string>
    <string name="clothesQ6">Do you wear the same style of clothes on the weekend and on the weekdays?</string>
    <string name="clothesA6">No, definitely not as I am a student and I have to wear a uniform on weekdays but on weekends I just wear t-shirts with trousers while staying at home that is more comfortable for me.</string>
    <string name="clothesQ7">Do you wear the same clothes at school/work?</string>
    <string name="clothesA7">At school, I usually wear school uniforms, and it is very boring to wear the same uniform all day.</string>
    <string name="clothesQ8">Did you have any special clothes when you were a child?</string>
    <string name="clothesA8">Yes, of course, I remember that there was an annual function in my school when I was in 2nd grade, and I took part in that. So, my mother made beautiful clothes for me to wear on that occasion which was very special for me because it was so attractive.</string>

    //Daily Routine
    <string name="daily_routineQ1">When do you wake up?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA1">Well, I\’m a morning riser, and I wake up at about 5 o’clock. Getting up early not only makes me feel refreshed and productive, but also prevents my skin from having wrinkles.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ2">What is your daily routine?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA2">Well, in the morning, I get up early to have a light breakfast and hit the gym at about 8 a.m. After one hour of workout, I leave the gym club and go to the supermarket to buy food to prepare lunch and dinner. In the afternoon and evening, I go to my workplace and start working from 14.00.pm until 21.00.p.m.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ3">What part of the day do you like most?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA3">I enjoy it late at night when I come home from work, and everything is filled with dim grey light. To me, it\’s a great time to kick back on the bed to have a chit-chat with my roommates, surf the Internet, listen to music, or watch a favorite movie.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ4">Do you think it is important to have a daily routine?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA4">Yes, it is. A proper daily routine will help you arrange your activities most sensibly. Without a daily routine, people usually do things spontaneously, which could waste their time and reduce their work efficiency. I think those who are disorganized can gain more benefits from creating a daily routine.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ5">What\’s the difference in routine between you and your teenage times?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA5">Well, I can say that there\’s a vast difference between my life then and my present life. You know, when I was a teenager, besides focusing on study, I had much free time to pursue my interests like watching films or listening to music. In contrast, my routine and time management have become stricter now. Since I graduated from university and began working as an English teacher, I\’m so occupied with my work that I have little leisure time.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ6">What is the busiest part of the day for you?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA6">Afternoons are the busiest time of the day for me. I work for a UK company and my day starts at 2:00 PM. So by 3:00 PM I will be bombarded with client calls and emails and will have no time to breathe.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ7">Do you usually have the same routine every day? (or) Do you usually do the same things at the same time each day?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA7">Mostly yes. I\’m an early bird though I go late to bed. On weekdays, my work starts at 2:00 PM and I wind up by 11:00 PM. On weekends, I go shopping and sleep a little early. I follow this schedule every week and there aren\’t any major changes unless we have celebrations.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ8">Have you ever changed your routine?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA8">Yes, it changed about a month ago. I had a very tight schedule and was struggling to manage my targets. So I had to work late until 2:00 AM.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ9">What would you like to change in your daily routine?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA9">My work starts at 2:00 PM. So I laze around until then. I want to use that time productively. Some of my friends go to the gym and I would like to start an exercise regime as well.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ10">Do you like to plan what you will do each day?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA10">Yes, I would like to. Planning keeps the day in your control. The more organized you are, the better your life becomes. I\’m pretty orderly at work and I want to be the same way in my other activities as well.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ11">What do you usually do at this time of day?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA11">It is 10:30 AM now. You can find me watching television or reading a magazine. Sometimes I go out and talk to my friends.</string>
    <string name="daily_routineQ12">How do you organize your study time?</string>
    <string name="daily_routineA12">I’m pursuing a course in Management along with my work. I usually study on the weekends because I want an entire day to myself. I don\’t study on weekdays as it becomes stressful.</string>

    //Food
    <string name="foodQ1">What kind of food do you like to eat? </string>
    <string name="foodA1">I mostly like homemade foods. They are hygienic, made from organic sources and have no chemicals or adhesive. However, my preference in homemade foods does not discourage me to dine outside. I prefer having dinner in a Chinese or Italian restaurant as I love their menu. I am also fond of Pizza and Sandwich.</string>
    <string name="foodQ2">What kind of new food would you like to try? Why?</string>
    <string name="foodA2">I have never tried Thai foods and I would love to taste it. One of my cousins is very fond of Thai foods and he had convinced me that I should give it a try. I think I would like it. I have a plan to take my family to a renowned restaurant in our city to taste the Thai foods together. Apart from that, I would love to try Japanese Sushi. I have heard so much about it but have never tasted it.</string>
    <string name="foodQ3">Do you like cooking? Why/ Why not?</string>
    <string name="foodA3">I love cooking. This is sometimes very relaxing and gives a good feeling. I do not need to cook very often but when I do, I feel like I kind of enjoy it. Maybe if I had to cook every day, my opinion could have been different! My mom mostly cooks in our house and whenever I declare that I would cook either for lunch or dinner, my brothers and sisters become excited and worried at the same time. They love the way I try to cook different menu each time and they often find my cooking tasty but they also remember some of the incidents when my foods tasted horrible. But if you ask me whether I enjoy cooking, I would say yes, and I like doing experiments no matter what others think about it.</string>
    <string name="foodQ4">What was the last meal you cooked?</string>
    <string name="foodA4">That must be more than 3 months since I cooked last time. It was fried rice with eggs, prawn and vegetables. I also cooked mutton with curry and as a desert, I made apple pie. Fortunately, this time, my siblings were pleased with my cooking!!!</string>
    <string name="foodQ5">Do you prefer home-cooked food or food from restaurants? Why?</string>
    <string name="foodA5">As I said my preference is home-cooked foods over outside foods. My father does not like the idea of having outside meals that often. Apart from that, my mother is an excellent cook and we enjoy her menu a lot. Outside foods are quite expensive and not fully hygienic. This is why all of my family members prefer home-made foods.</string>
    <string name="foodQ6">What are some kinds of food you never eat? Why?</string>
    <string name="foodA6">Stuffed peppers, pan-fried Scottish scallops served with tomato relish, salmon mollee, Japanese Sushi, popadums, Sour cream and Chive fries and Shrimp cocktails are some of the food items I have never eaten. Most of these items are not common in our city and I have heard about those menus from my friends. Since they are not available in our city and I do not have an extensive travelling experience, I did not get the chance to take them.</string>
    <string name="foodQ7">What are some reasons that people eat at a restaurant?</string>
    <string name="foodA7">Eating at a restaurant offers people to enjoy the foods as well as the views and surrounding. They do not need to cook and foods are usually delicious. People are treated well in a restaurant and people love that a lot. We can invite as many people as we want in a restaurant and we do not need to clean anything unlike eating at home. There are a variety of menus to choose from and people can enjoy exotic foods at a restaurant that are not usually cooked at home. We can meet friends and other relatives at a restaurant and enjoy our conversation without interruption. I think those are the main reasons we like to eat out in a restaurant even though we have to pay a large amount of money for the foods we eat.</string>
    <string name="foodQ8">Describe a popular food in your country? Why do people like this food?</string>
    <string name="foodA8">Pizza is most probably one of the most popular food items in my county. This was not on the list of popular food items probably 10 years back, but the popularity of pizza, especially, among young people is unbelievable nowadays. The popularity is probably because of its taste and easy availability. Every corner of a street has a fast food shop in my town and they sell pizza. Craze among young generation about the fast food items, especially pizza, is another reason it is so popular in my country.</string>
    <string name="foodQ9">What kinds of food do you particularly like?</string>
    <string name="foodA9">I\’d have to say Asian cuisine is my favorite. I am a huge fan of the bold flavors and spices used in Korean and Vietnamese dishes. Something I often daydream about eating is X, which is a tip-smacking noodle soup dish served with a crab broth. It\’s every bit as delicious as it sounds.</string>
    <string name="foodQ10">Is there any food you don\’t like?</string>
    <string name="foodA10">It\’s true that there are a few things that kind of put me off. For example, I cannot stand Y, which is essentially a shrimp paste. A lot of people like it, though, but I think it smells awful. Definitely not my cup of tea.</string>
    <string name="foodQ11">What kinds of food are most popular in your country?</string>
    <string name="foodA11">I think street food is a staple around here. You can find bustling food stalls all around our nation, and they are my go-tos for a cheap and cheerful meal. I mean gourmet restaurants are nice and all, but street food is what our country is all about.</string>
    <string name="foodQ12">Do you like cooking? (Why?/ Why not?)</string>
    <string name="foodA12">Actually, I\’d like to think that cooking is my forte. I developed a passion for culinary arts when I first watched the cooking show Masterchef. Since then, I have learnt a lot of recipes and I can easily whip up a good dinner.</string>

    //hobbies
    <string name="hobbyQ1">Do you have any hobbies?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA1">Well, everyone has their own leisure pursuits, and mine is reading. The book I\’m reading at the moment is The Godfather by renowned author Mario Puzo. It\’s a classic, really, and I\’d recommend it.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ2">Is it important to have a hobby?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA2">Definitely! I mean nowadays life is getting more and more hectic, so people are always under an enormous amount of stress. That\’s why it\’s helpful to get into some recreational activities to be able to unwind and just forget about life for a minute, you know?</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ3">Is it harmful to spend too much time on a hobby?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA3">Yes, I believe spending excessive time on a hobby may have an adverse effect on people. You may end up having not enough time for your priorities like family or work. For example, it\’s easy for me to lose myself in books and neglect the deadlines at work.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ4">What free-time activities would you like to try in the future?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA4">I would love to have a crack at extreme sports in the future, maybe ski-diving. It looks like a blast and I think I will get a real kick out of free-falling from enormous heights.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ5">Do you have a hobby?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA5">Yes, I have numerous hobbies such as reading books, playing cricket, adventure sports, Art and craft activities.After that my favourite hobby is reading books as well as with the help of reading books I can enhance my knowledge and vocabulary.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ6">What equipment do you need for it?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA6">Well, there are many advanced tools that we need when we want to paint something, such as paintbrushes and painting surfaces like canvas, wood, or others.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ7">Do you think hobbies should be shared with other people?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA7">Yeah, we do hobbies to enjoy, for fun purposes, we will feel happy because of it, so by sharing our hobby with another person, I think, it could make them happy as well.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ8">Did you have a hobby as a child?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA8">Yes, in my childhood I have so many hobbies. During my childhood, my favourite hobby is playing badminton and watching tv shows. Apart from that, I utilize my all-time to play badminton.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ9">What hobbies are popular in your country?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA9">Well, there are a number of hobbies that are famous in my nation, such as indoor and outdoor games, adventure sports, art and craft activities. Further, in my nation different people like the different types of hobbies. Apart from it, mostly youngsters like to do adventures sports, as well as the girls, like to do animation and indoor games. So that\’s why people like hobbies according to your choice.</string>
    <string name="hobbyQ10">Why do you think people have hobbies?</string>
    <string name="hobbyA10">Well, Hobbies is the best way to utilize their leisure time. Apart from that, hobbies help them to relieve tension and stress After doing the hobbies, people can maintain their body as well as they can share their talent with others. So hobbies play an indispensable role in human life.</string>

    //internet
    <string name="internetQ1">How important is the internet to you?</string>
    <string name="internetA1">Extremely important. I depend on it for work, research, study and entertainment, so without it I\’d be complete lost.</string>
    <string name="internetQ2">How often do you use the internet?</string>
    <string name="internetA2">I use it constantly throughout the day, every day. I check my emails when I get up in the morning, I use it for work all day and then I watch videos, read books or listen to music through it at night.</string>
    <string name="internetQ3">What are your favourite websites?</string>
    <string name="internetA3">For work my two favourite sites are WordPress and Google. WordPress is a blogging tool that allows you to publish blogs easily and maintain a professional looking website. Google of course allows me to find the information I need quickly and accurately. In my spare time, I of course use Facebook like everyone else in the world, but my favourite site is The Guardian because it allows me to keep up to date with everything that\’s happening.</string>
    <string name="internetQ4">Do you use apps?</string>
    <string name="internetA4">I\’m a bit of an app addict. My favourite app at the moment is one called Stitcher. It allows you to listen to podcasts and helps you discover new podcasts. You can download them and then listen to them whenever you have time.</string>
    <string name="internetQ5">Do you think you use the internet too much?</string>
    <string name="internetA5">I think most people do these days. My problem is that there are so many sites and apps that you end up checking them way too often and this wastes lots of time. It can also be a bit anti-social if you are checking your phone all the time when you are with other people.</string>
    <string name="internetQ6">How will the internet develop in the future?</string>
    <string name="internetA6">I think it will be more on mobile phones than computers. Smart phones are becoming more powerful and more affordable all the time, so I think we will see a shift from people using the internet on desktop computers to mobiles and apps rather than traditional websites.</string>
    <string name="internetQ7">Are there any negative things about the internet?</string>
    <string name="internetA7">Being connected all of the time is not a good thing. Before you had to sit down at your computer and log on and that took time, so you didn\’t do it so much. Now all people have to do is look at their phone and this is too much for me. I\’ve been trying to leave my phone at home when I socialise with friends and family to stop myself from focusing too much on the phone rather than them</string>
    <string name="internetQ8">How important is Internet to you?</string>
    <string name="internetA8">The Internet is like a staple food for me; I use this thing almost all the time, for work, study, and a lot of other things.</string>
    <string name="internetQ9">Do you use the Internet more for work or in your free time?</string>
    <string name="internetA9">during my free time, I usually prefer to relax and surf on any social media application unless it is necessary to complete the work within a limited deadline.</string>
    <string name="internetQ10">Do you think you use Internet too much?</string>
    <string name="internetA10">Definitely, I am a person deeply involved in social networking hence requires too much internet than a normal user.</string>
    <string name="internetQ11">How will Internet develop in the future?</string>
    <string name="internetA11">Well, with the increase of Internet users, the Internet in the future will reach all people around the world, although in deserts, mountains, deep forests, or even in the deep of the ocean, people are able to use the Internet without any hesitation in connection.</string>

    //Leisure time
    <string name="leisure_timeQ1">What do you do in your spare time?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA1">It varies, I mean, it depends on the amount of free time I have. A few weeks ago, I would normally immerse myself in a light novel during lunch breaks or after dinner, but these days, I’m just too busy with my work that the only thing I crave is some sleep, so all my spare time would be devoted to taking a quick nap.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ2">What do you do to relax?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA2">These days, I’ve been suffering from severe stress and depression due to the excessive amount of workload I have, and the only time I can relax is during my 4 – 5 hours of sleep every night. So, it may sound a little bit weird, but the only thing I can do to relax is, sadly, sleep.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ3">How do you usually spend your weekends?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA3">I\’m not a party animal, so during weekends, I always refuse all the party invitations from my friends. Instead, I would visit a café on my own and indulge myself with a nice cup of earl grey and some new book I\’ve found on Amazon. That couldn\’t be more perfect for a Sunday afternoon.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ4">What do you usually do after work or classes?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA4">I work evening shifts, so on a daily basis, I stop at around 9 p.m. and leave work 15 – 30 minutes later. At that time, most shops have already closed and there’re not many recreational activities left to do if you don’t want to hang around bars, so I often go straight home to take a hot shower and have a late dinner. Once in a while, my boyfriend would take me to the movies after work, but I would fall asleep half way through the film.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ5">How much time do you have each week for doing these things?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA5">If your asking for a specific number of hours, I guess I\’d have to say just a couple of hours per day probably.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ6">Why do you like doing these activities?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA6">I don\’t. I mean… who would like to go back home right after work just to have a late, cold, and sometimes leftover dinner? That\’s just what I have to do since I have to work until late in the evening. I\’m not allowed to choose, that\’s the problem.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ7">How did you start doing this activity at first?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA7">Actually, my life didn\’t used to revolve around work. A few years ago I used to lead quite a busy social life, back in university, so it took me a whole year to get used to my current lifestyle. So, I think everything has just become a routine to me now. Not in a natural way, but it has.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ8">Is there some other hobby or sport you would like to try? Why?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA8">I\’m crazy about music and all kinds of musical instruments. It\’s such a miracle how each instrument makes a different sound, but when they\’re performed together, they can create perfect combinations of melodies. Perhaps, in the near future, I would learn about the mechanism behind this miracle. This is also a hobby, isn\’t it?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ9">How do you spend your time in the evening?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA9">It\’s the same every day. I just keep running around in circles: going to work, coming back home, working at home, then going back to work the next morning. That\’s why the evening is, somehow, just another chance for me to satisfy my workaholic self. That\’s it.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ10">Do you prefer staying at home or going out during evenings?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA10">It\’s like an everyday dilemma. My heart always insists me to go out and have some fun, but my mind would say no to that seemingly irrational idea. Well, my deadlines are there, my work isn\’t finished. So, most of the time, I would reluctantly stay home.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ11">Do you do this every evening?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA11">I hate to admit, but yes, every evening when I have work left unfinished. Sometimes, I\’ve even done all my make-up and already gotten dressed. However, while waiting for my boyfriend to pick me up, I often change my mind and go back to my work instead.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ12">What do you like to do on the weekends?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA12">As I\’ve mentioned earlier, I\’m quite a loner and I really enjoy that part of myself. So, during weekends, I would usually find something to do on my own, like redecorating my room, going to a café all alone, or just find a quiet spot in my house to do some crosswords and quizzes. I just really love to enjoy time by myself.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ13">Is there any difference in your life now from when you were a child?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA13">This is an intriguing question, since I honestly don\’t know what to tell you. But overall, my life has changed considerably compared to what it was throughout my childhood. Everything, from my feelings, my thoughts to my relationships or accommodation, is so different now that I nearly have no recollections about the past.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ14">Do you think modern lifestyles give people enough time for leisure?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA14">It\’s hard to say. Nowadays, people can have access to more and more entertainment facilities, and these facilities can accommodate our demands for recreation at any time. That\’s why it\’s become harder to distinguish between working hours and leisure time, which means you can\’t really tell whether the current lifestyles can give people an adequate amount of time for leisure.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ15">Do you think people today have more time to relax compared to the past?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA15">We do have more time to relax now compared with the amount we had in the past thanks to a great number of technological advances, which are gradually replacing people\’s involvement in many fields. However, many people now are refusing to take a break, perhaps because they just don\’t want to be made redundant in the modern society.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ16">What do you think is the importance of leisure time in life?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA16">Adequate and frequent leisure time keeps our lives balanced. What I mean is if we just stay focused on our work and study without proper relaxation, we would eventually find ourselves exhausted and may suffer from all kinds of mental conditions related to stress, like depression or bipolar disorder. So, I do believe that leisure time plays an integral part in people\’s lives.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ17">Do you think old and young people spend their leisure time in the same way?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA17">Unfortunately, no. Family bonds would be strengthened significantly if this happened in real life. However, it\’s no surprise that the youth and the elderly hardly ever share the same interests due to the huge generation gap, so there\’s no chance they would do the same thing in their spare time. You\’re most likely to find youngsters on their phones, and on the other hand, old people would often be found doing some conventional activities for leisure like playing chess or knitting.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ18">Do you like to travel in holidays?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA18">As long as it’s a long holiday, for example, Tet, or summer holiday. I just honestly don\’t want to go away for just 2 – 3 days because that would leave me no time to enjoy myself.</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeQ19">If you had a child, what leisure places would you go with your child?</string>
    <string name="leisure_timeA19">Well, I know children are often crazy about amusement parks and if I had children I suppose they would definitely beg me to take them there. Unfortunately, I can\’t stand crowded and noisy places, so maybe instead of that, I would take my kids to some leafy area, like a national park or botanic gardens, where we could discover more about nature.</string>

    //music
    <string name="musicQ1">Do you often (like to) listen to music?</string>
    <string name="musicA1">So far I haven\’t met anyone who dislikes music. However, when the workload is too heavy that requires me to stay highly focused, music is a huge distraction. Unlike many people who listen to instrumental music because it helps them focus,  music makes me feel sleepy.</string>
    <string name="musicQ2">When do you listen to music?</string>
    <string name="musicA2">Well, the whole world likes it, so I\’m no exception. I usually listen to cheerful music when I need motivation and prefer sad ones, when I\’m in a bad mood.</string>
    <string name="musicQ3">How much time do you spend listening to music every day?</string>
    <string name="musicA3">As I\’ve mentioned I prefer working in silence. To put it simply, I don\’t listen to music during my working hours. After a long day at school, I probably want to chill out for like half an hour and music helps me to stay energetic.</string>
    <string name="musicQ4">What kinds of music do you like to listen to? Or What\’s your favourite kind of music?</string>
    <string name="musicA4">I prefer a range of music from Western to Eastern, and from the 90s to modern EDM. But if Korean pop is considered as a kind of music, then yeah, that\’s my favourite. More than half of my playlists are Korean songs and I always keep myself updated with news related to Korean showbiz.</string>
    <string name="musicQ5">Have you ever been to a concert before? Or Have you ever been to a musical performance?</string>
    <string name="musicA5">I attend concerts, once in a blue moon, since the ticket price for foreign artists\’ concerts is out of my reach.  So I can only stay home and watch online. It was in 2014 that I finally did go to a concert on my own and it was an international music concert. It was absolutely mind-blowing and an unforgettable experience.</string>
    <string name="musicQ6">Do you like to listen to live music?</string>
    <string name="musicA6">Unless it\’s live at a coffee shop, where literally there is only music and me, then yeah I would love to. But I would change my mind if it\’s a concert. The crowd is too crazy. It\’s completely a mess most of the time and I end up with a severe headache.</string>
    <string name="musicQ7">When did you start listening to this type of music?</string>
    <string name="musicA7">From the day a friend of mine introduced her favourite group to me. She couldn\’t help herself talking on and on about them that I thought I somehow needed to catch up with her. And the more I got to know about Korean pop, the more passionate I became.</string>
    <string name="musicQ8">Where do you listen to it?</string>
    <string name="musicA8">Almost everywhere, except for the classroom. It\’s the golden era of mobile devices. Everyone carries earphone and phones with them all the time, music, therefore, is on their fingertips.</string>
    <string name="musicQ9">How do you feel when you listen to this music?</string>
    <string name="musicA9">Well, I\’m the type of person whose mood is easily affected by what I\’m listening to. Thus as the music changes, my mood also fluctuates. But most of the time, listening to some music helps me pick up my energy and chill a bit.</string>
    <string name="musicQ10">Have you ever learned to play a musical instrument?</string>
    <string name="musicA10">I learned to play the organ when I was in kindergarten. It was quite funny because I started out as one of the performers. Then my teacher told my mom that I had better play the organ instead of performing. So I became her trainee and it continued for around 4 to 5 years until I was 10.</string>
    <string name="musicQ11">Is music an important subject at school in your country?</string>
    <string name="musicA11">Music is one of the compulsory subjects for primary and secondary students in my country. However, the main focus was on singing. We could also add some movements to make the songs more lively. Only those who were selected for the large performances were allowed to use musical instruments.</string>
    <string name="musicQ12">Did you often listen to music when you were a child?</string>
    <string name="musicA12">Since my parents are music-lovers and also have very good tastes, I was exposed to music at a very young age. Sometimes my mom sang me to sleep with her lullabies. Although I could not get the message at that time, my mom said that I buoyed up when listening to them.</string>
    <string name="musicQ13">What kinds of music are (most) popular in your country?</string>
    <string name="musicA13">Besides pop music, the younger generation nowadays is exposed to different types of music. It is indeed difficult to tell which is in-demand since I feel each type has roughly the same popularity. But I guess pop music is the most sought-after now. I\’ve never met someone who doesn\’t know pop songs.</string>
    <string name="musicQ14">Do you like traditional songs?</string>
    <string name="musicA14">Well, it\’s easy for me to name some traditional songs, some of which I\’m very familiar with. But to be honest, I think I\’m not that into this kind of music.</string>

    //shopping
    <string name="shoppingQ1">Do you like shopping?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA1">Yeah, I do like shopping a lot since it helps us to get new stuffs for ourselves all the time.</string>
    <string name="shoppingQ2">What\’s your favourite shop?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA2">I really like clothing shops since the items there are very decorative and eye-catching items, and it comes with different types of items for which you would like to take any and makes shopping difficult for you.</string>
    <string name="shoppingQ3">Do you prefer shopping alone or with others?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA3">Shopping with someone has always been my most preferred way to shop since you would not be left alone and also would definitely get someone you trust with you to help you make choices.</string>
    <string name="shoppingQ4">What kinds of shops are there where you live?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA4">I live in a rural area, and there are not many shops around, but we have book shops, electrical and clothing shops</string>
    <string name="shoppingQ5">Have you ever bought anything online?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA5">Yeah, I did buy an SD Card once from an online store that was recommended to me by a friend.</string>
    <string name="shoppingQ6">Do you think men and women have different opinions about shopping?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA6">Definitely, because men would like to get themselves a few items to change their wardrobe or the likes, but ladies always want to change their whole wardrobe.</string>
    <string name="shoppingQ7">Do you enjoy shopping?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA7">Yes, I\’m a massive fan of shopping. Actually, I\’d say that I\’m a bit of a shopaholic. I absolutely love to try on and buy new clothes. I used to go on shopping sprees every month, but because I was spending too much money, I had to cut down. </string>
    <string name="shoppingQ8">What are your favorite stores?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA8">As mentioned, I\’ve become more frugal, so I tend to go for reasonably-priced high-street stores.I suppose my favorite shop is HM. It\’s good value for money and they always stock the latest trends.</string>
    <string name="shoppingQ9">Have you bought anything online?</string>
    <string name="shoppingA9">Yes, I have purchased some gadgets. Last year, I bought my phone from an online retailer as it was much better value there than in a brick and mortar store.  I\'d like to buy clothes online, but I\’m always afraid that when delivered, they won\’t fit me.</string>

    <string name="sample_answer_part1">Sample answer is shown here. It doesn\'t matter how much line it requires, it should show all line</string>
    <string name="part_1_sample_answer">Part 1 sample answer</string>
    <string name="part_2_sample_answer">Part 2 sample answer</string>
    <string name="pronunciation">Pronunciation</string>
</resources>